# AMRIT KHAREL

**DEVELOPER** 

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Web Development
Mobile Deevelopment
Networking
Data Analyst
Programming
Algorothims, Data Structure and
OS programming
User of All Three Major OS
Version control: GIT and Bit
Bucket
Database Managment
Cloud Platform
Web Server

### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Creative spirit Reliable and professional Organized Team player Fast learner Motivated

### CONTACT

0451279032 amrit.kharel6@gmail.com www.developerenvironment.com

### REFEREES

Avilable on Request

#### **PROFILE**

A Developer who loves to learn and explore new ideas and concepts. Able to adapt, work alone as well as in a Team to enhance workflow. Worked in Professional Environment with responsibility for completing the task and addressing to supervisor.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **NOTEBOOK SOLUTION & ALPHAZONE COMPUTERS**

2016-2017

- Dealing with customer issues such as queries and complaints.
- Installing, configuring, and troubleshooting Windows, Linux, and MAC.
- Perform backups, installation of software, and fix hardware issues.
- Support customers with technology services and digital access to information supplied
- Troubleshoot base technical issues with end-user hardware, software, and services
- Visit onsite and fulfill customers' needs for ICT enquires.

#### **PAXFORM**

2021- Ongoing

- Planning and developing Flow Chart for Features and business function
- Following Figma UI to develop Front end of the App.
- Using Bit Bucket for version control. Experienced with Merge, Push, Stack, and Branch.
- Using Flutter, Laravel API to Develop App.
- Developing Features and contributing to Whole project
- Analysing readability of the code and reporting to supervisor.

#### **EDUCATION**

# CERTIFICATE III IN INFORMATION AND DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY

TAFE NSW | 2016 - 2017

# BACHELOR OF INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY

Major in Mobile Computing
Sub-Major in Social Media Analytics and Networking
University of Western Sydney | 2018 - 2020